Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Outgoing Correspondence Index
  - Bruce, William C., April 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., April 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Keboch, F.D., April 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ellis, Mabel Brown, April 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., April 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bruce, William C., April 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ludlow and Peabody, Architects, April 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mandel Brothers, April 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - National Incinerator Co., April 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Sanford, E.C., April 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mark, E.H., April 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Wales C., April 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bruce, William C., April 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., April 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Pullman Automatic Ventilator, April 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.F., April 30, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., May 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Jassop, W.H., May 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, Ruben, May 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., May 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., May 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ittner, William B., May 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., May 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Yasinski, A.F., May 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Culver County Public Schools, May 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., May 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., May 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Henry E., May 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., May 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Morris, Agnes, May 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Virtue and Co., May 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., May 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McClain, E.L., May 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., May 19, 1913 (Box 1)
  - James, George F., May 19, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doelle, Jonathan A., May 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., May 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Richardson, Mr. and Mrs. J.B., May 31, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bierly, H.E., June 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Henry E., June 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.O., June 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Gignilliat, L.R., June 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - James, George F., June 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mundy, H.H., June 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Storey, Thomas A., June 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Virtue and Co., June 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, C.H., June 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., June 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Gunn, Selskar M., June 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Walker, W.B., Jr., June 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., June 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mundy, H.H., June 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Conditt, Abbie, June 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Corwin, R.W., June 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ellis, Mabel Brown, June 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Fuii,W.G., June 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Walker, W.B., June 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., June 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Wales C., June 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, Charles H., June 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., June 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., June 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Perkins, D.H., June 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., June 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Springer, D.W., June 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., June 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Houghton Mifflin Co., June 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rail, E.E., June 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Conditt, Abbie, June 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Burnham, William C., June 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Doelle, Jonathan A., June 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Houghton Mifflin Co., June 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Perkins, D.H., June 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., June 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., June 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Callahan, E.L., June 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Corwin, R.W., June 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., June 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hodgson, Casper W., June 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., June 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Vogel, H.G., June 16, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Dobbyn, F.W., June 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wray, George B., June 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., June 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Callahan, E.B., June 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Elliott, E.F., June 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mundy, H.H., June 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Walker, W.B., Jr., June 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, W.C., June 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, L.D., June 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Miller, Donald H., June 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Winship, A.E., June 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ludlow and Peabody, Architects, June 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bogan, William J., Sept. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Broome, Joseph, Sept. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cheney, Charles Henry, Sept. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Walcott, J.D., Sept. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Berry, M.W., Sept. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Brower, A.S., Sept. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Coggin, Mrs. S.R., Sept. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cooke, John W., Sept. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach (sic), L.A., Sept. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rapeer, Lewis, Sept. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rich, Josephine Arnold, Sept. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Shute, Mrs. H.J., Sept. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Sept. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Che Plakas, Constantin, Sept. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Humphrey, Mrs. Charles G., Sept. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Tharp, S.M., Sept. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cook, John W., Sept. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Fitzpatrick, F.B., Sept. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Holland, E.O., Sept. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Perkins, Fellows and Hamilton, Sept. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Platt, J. Mills, Sept. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Baruch, Bertha Hirsch, Sept. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Bateman, Mrs. C.C., Sept. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hyatt, Edward, Sept. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Naramore, F.A., Sept. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ellis, Carlos B., Sept. 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ellis, Carlos B., Sept. 23, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - O'Neil, J.H., Sept. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mairs, Thomas I., Sept. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Alltucker, Margaret M., Sept. 25, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Chapin, Clara C., Sept. 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cherry, H.H., Sept. 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Sept. 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Engelhard, V.H., Sept. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ferrell, John A., Sept. 27, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hanson-Bellows Co., Oct. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kingsley, Sherman, Oct. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Parks, M.M., Dec. 5, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Peterson, E.A., Dec. 12, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Kelly, RoyW., Dec. 15, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Finney, Ross L., Dec. 21, 1917 (Box 2)
  - Baker, N.R., Jan. 7, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Alice H., Jan. 15, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Jan. 15, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Boykin, J.C., Jan. 16, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Chapman, J. Virgil, Jan. 16, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Jan. 16, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Haltom, L.H., Jan. 21, 1918 (Box 2)
  - Crichlow, J.H., Jan. 23, 1918 (Box 2)
  - Regen and Weller, Architects, Feb. 1, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Woodden, Eli, Feb. 9, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Woodden, Eli, Feb. 9, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 14, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Luckie, W.V., Feb. 14, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Ramsey, J.W., Feb. 19, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Boykin, NFN, March 7, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Elizabeth McCormick Memorial, March 7, 1918 (Box 2)
  - Small, Willard S., March 23, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Bush, L.L., March 28, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Denney, C.C., April 4, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Carter, E.E., April 17, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, Margaret Y., April 17, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Wright, Owen B., April 17, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Treen, Karl, April 26, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Vermilion, H.F., April 26, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., May 14, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Bower, Grover C., May 18, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Frank Irving, May 22, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 7, 1918 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., July 20, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Stewart, NFN, July 27, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Waller, George D., Aug. 9, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., Aug. 26, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Gilbert, H.C., Aug. 29, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Spratling, Mrs. M.A., Aug. 29, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 14, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Dean, L.A., Sept. 14, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Johnson, Helen Lansing, Sept. 14, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Dean, L.A., Sept. 20, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Dean, L.A., Sept. 26, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Dean, L.A., Oct. 16, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Windes, E.E., Oct. 16, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Dean, L.A., Nov. 8, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Chenault, Robert N., Dec. 13, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Dukes, A.J., Dec. 13, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Foster, James, Dec. 13, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Foster, James, Dec. 13, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Pontius, Isaac, Jan. 16, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Decker, A. I., Jan. 10, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Buckley, H.M., Jan. 25, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Dowell, Spright, Jan. 27, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Buice, W.A., Jan. 29, 1918 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Feb. 1, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, E.B., Feb. 1, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Manley, J.B., Feb. 3, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Minkel, L.H., Feb. 6, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Blackwell, Walter R.L., Feb. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Johnson, W.P., Feb. 15, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Buckley, H.M., Feb. 19, 1919 (Box 2)
  - North, E.M., Feb. 24, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Reynolds, R.J., Feb. 24, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Threlfall, LV., March 4, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Parsons, Mary S., March 7, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Patterson, E.W., March 7, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Baker, N.R., March 18, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Daniel, R.P., March 18, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Perrin, Ambrose, March 18, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Bedford, Lois, March 24, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, William T., April?, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Tucker, E.B., April?, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Friffee, Arthur H., April 10, 1919 (Box 3)
  - John Latenser and Sons, April 10, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., April 10, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Wilder, Theo, April 10, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Morrison, W.P., April 16, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Bennett, Twitty and Reese, May 8, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Buice, W.A., May 8, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Duffey, H.S., May 8, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Wolcott, Theresa H., May 8, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Lavery, D., May 19, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Thomas, David E., May 20, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Bennett, Twitty and Reese, May 21, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., June 7, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Mead, Clarence G., June 7, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Blakeley, H.B., June 16, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Chamblis, R. Lee, June 16, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Walter E., June 16, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Bennett, Twitty and Reese, June 18, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Griggs, W.C., Sept. 27, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Bryan, T.J., Sept. 29, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Rupert, W.W., Sept. 29, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Cherry, H.H., Oct. 1, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Able, J.F., Oct. 16, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Lola, Oct. 16, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Woodring, A.P., Oct. 16, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Griggs, W.C., Oct. 18, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Rupert, W.W., Oct. 18, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Lucey, Michael H., Oct. 26, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Stoltzfus, J.H., Oct. 26, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Easley, Owen R., Oct. 30, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Morrison, W.J., Oct. 30, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Rhodes, L.T., Oct. 30, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Rosenkoeter, C.H., Oct. 30, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Stone, May, Oct. 30, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Chenault, Robert N., Oct. 31, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Cowart, R.W., Nov. 1, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Gove, W.E., Nov. 1, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Cheanult, Robert N., Nov. 4, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Clayton, Aline, Nov. 4, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Nov. 4, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Brunimer, Rose L., Nov. 17, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Harrington, A.C., Nov. 17, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Henry, Esther E., Nov. 17, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Hovey, George Rice, Nov. 17, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Cameron, Norman W., Nov. 19, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Cummings, Grace, Nov. 19, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Imhof, Orris M., Nov. 19, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Seizer, F.l., Nov. 20, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Mills, Hubert H., Nov. 21, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Suhrie, Ambrose L., Nov. 21, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Todd, John W., Nov. 21, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Yelland, W.R., Nov. 21, 1919 (Box 3)
  - McLellan, J.B., Nov. 22, 1919 (Box 3)
  - McQuilkin, D.E., Nov. 22, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Griggs, W.C., Nov. 24, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Shackelford, E.M., Dec. 1, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Sharp, L.A., Dec. 1, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Chenault, Robert N., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Corbin, A.F., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Cowart, R.W., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Elliott, A.E., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Griggs, Mr., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Jenkins, L.W., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Jones, R.R., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - McClellan, J.B., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Netcott and Netcott, Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Redfern, J.E., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Stegal, B.M., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Tighe, Richard J., Dec. 13, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Atkinson, Otto, Dec. 15, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Baker, N.R., Dec. 23, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Carpenter, Harry A., Dec. 23, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Earl, E.O., Dec. 23, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Eichelberger, James W., Dec. 23, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Pelton, A.C., Dec. 23, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Robinson, William McKinley, Dec. 23, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Sharp, L.A., Dec. 23, 1919 (Box 3)
  - Holt, Elizabeth C., Jan. 5, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Howell, Harry, Feb. 26, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Chapman, Virgil, March 4, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Holt, Elizabeth, March 11, 192 (Box 3)
  - Pratt, Linwood, March 19, 192 (Box 3)
  - Moore, W.E., April 29, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Holt, Elizabeth C., June 3, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Twiss, George I., June 16, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Phelps, C.E., June 22, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Nash, Mary E., June 30, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Temple, H.R., June 30, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., July 1, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., July 27, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, W.T., Aug. 3, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Beckham, Mary C., Aug. 3, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, W.T., Aug. 14, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Lowrey, Harvey H., Sept. 20, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Calhoun, J.T., Nov. 1, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Holt, Elizabeth C., Nov. 27, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Keller, W.K., Nov. 27, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Miller, W.E., Dec. 12, 1920 (Box 3)
  - Avent, Joseph E., Jan. 8, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Unidentified, Jan. 15, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Page, Frank R., Jan. 20, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Stephens, Edwin L., Jan. 20, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Cater, Anna L., Feb. 7, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Hildebrandt, H.A., Feb. 7, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Schnittkind, Henry T., Feb. 26, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Schnittkind, Henry T., Feb. 26, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Hall, Maurice C., March 7, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Ragle, Horace N., March 7, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Able, J.F., March 11, 192 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 11, 192 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., March 17, 192 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 17, 192 (Box 3)
  - Baker, B.B., March 24, 192 (Box 3)
  - Lang, A.B., March 24, 192 (Box 3)
  - Cady, Bertha Chapman, March 28, 192 (Box 3)
  - Cornwell, Irene M., March 28, 192 (Box 3)
  - King, Jeannette, March 31, 192 (Box 3)
  - Holt, Elizabeth C., April 6, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Ricker, Maurice, April 9, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Baker, B.B., April 23, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, William T., April 23, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Turner, Jessie, April 23, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Abercrombie, John W., April 25, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Benns, W.E., April 26, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Foote, Irving T., April 27, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Long, Raymond V., April 27, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Baker, B.B., April 30, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, William T., May 7, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Foote, Irving, May 30, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Tigert, John J., July 1, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Bischoff, Carl H., July 2, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Roberts, Ezra C., July 2, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Aug. 22, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Aug. 22, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Aug. 22, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Schnittkind, Henry T., Aug. 23, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Baker, Milo, Aug. 24, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Blair, John J., Sept. 3, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Sept. 3, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, Willard S., Sept. 6, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Blair, John J., Sept. 8, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Sept. 12, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Benson, W.W., Sept. 17, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Boykin, J.C., Sept. 21, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Sept. 22, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Sept. 22, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, Willard S., Sept. 22, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Freeman, J.E., Sept. 26, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Sept. 26, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Stephens, Dr., Setp. 26, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Oct. 5, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Smaii,Willard S., Oct. 10, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Oct. 26, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Oct. n.d., 1921 (Box 3)
  - Small, Willard S., Nov. 13, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Sibley, James L., Nov. 19, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Pennington, Pleasant, Nov. 29, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Spooner, H.L., Dec. 17, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Welborn, Allen, Dec. 17, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Blair, John J., Dec. 27, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Conner, W.A., Jan. 19, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Jan. 19, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Alice C., Jan. 19, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Dickey, Clarence W., Feb. 4, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Tigett, John J., Feb. 4, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Feb. 9, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Feb. 25, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., March 23, 192 (Box 3)
  - District Secretary, April 1, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., April 1, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Tappan, Julia B., April 1, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Walker, Robin A., April 1, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., April 24, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Tappan, Julie, April 24, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Madison, Frederick D., May 17, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., May 17, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., May 27, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Warnica, S.V., June 1, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Manufacturers' Record, June 15, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Snow, O.E., June 26, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Wolman, Abel, June 26, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Robinson, E.O., June 29, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Tigert, John J., July 1, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Harman, A. F., July 13, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Millison, J., July 20, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Tidball, Lewis C., July 20, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Surgeon General, July 22, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Lucas Jean, Sallie, Aug. 5, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Blair, John J., Sept. 11, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Hatcher, Lee, Sept. 11, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Wilby, Frank, Oct. 5, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Gould, Florence H., Oct. 7, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Roberts, J. Platt, Oct. 7, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Small, Willard S., Oct. 7, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Risley, James H., Oct. 11, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Buttrick, Wallace, Oct. 12, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Cook, A.E., Oct. 18, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Kate B., Oct. 18, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Oct. 18, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Martin, J.O., Oct. 19, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Kate B., Oct. 30, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Bogart, Peter B., Nov. 1, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Hill, Henry H., Nov. 1, 1922 (Box 3)
  - American Warming and Ventilatin, Nov. 23, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Klabach, L.A., Nov. 23, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Small, W.S., Nov. 23, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Carr, J.W., Dec. 6, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Wedgwood, Harriet, Dec. 6, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Wedgwood, Harriet, Dec. 13, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Neild, Edward F., Dec. 14, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Stillwell, Erie G., Dec. 14, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Wedgwood, Harriet, Jan. 5, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Frank Irving, Jan. 13, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Van Buskirk, E.F., Jan. 23, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Welborn, O.M., Feb. 5, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Lockhart, K.E., Feb. 15, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Betelle, James 0., March 1, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Abel, J.F., April 2, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, William T., April 2, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Cook, Katherine M., April 10, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Nunn, Roscoe, April 21, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Crittenden, B.K., April 28, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Long, Raymond V., April 28, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Kupfer, H.W., May 26, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, William T., June 14, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Hirst, C.M., June 14, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, William T., June 20, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Commissioner, June 25, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., July 2, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Oppen, Lucy, July 2, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., July 7, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Credle, W.F., July 9, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Allen, James E., July 25, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Ittner, W.B., Aug. 4, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Blair, J.J., Aug. 22, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Bawden, W.F., Aug. 30, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Blair, Jonathan J., Sept. 29, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Boykin, J.C., Sept. 29, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Boykin, J.C., Oct. 4, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Cooper, Frank Irving, Oct. 4, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Boykin, J.C., Oct. 5, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Kranz, J.R., Oct. 26, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Wedgwood, Harriet, Nov. 1, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Calhoun, J.T., Nov. 1, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Boykin, J.C., Nov. 8, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Horton, Rouchen, Nov. 8, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Moore, D.H., Nov. 26, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Ivy, H.M., Dec. 4, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Burris, Mr., Dec. 10, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Roemer, Joseph, Dec. 13, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Dec. 13, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Dec. 13, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Wright, C.K., Dec. 13, 1923 (Box 3)
  - Bethune, Mary M., Jan. 19, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 19, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Corbett, D.D., Jan. 19, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Macmillan Company, Jan. 19, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Ivy, H.M., March 4, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., March 5, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., March 5, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Russell, Frederick F., March 15, 192 (Box 3)
  - Bethune, Mary McCloud, March 20, 192 (Box 3)
  - Hinman, Jack J., Jr., April 14, 1924 (Box 3)
  - McAndrews, William, April 17, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Wimbs,Ad, April 28, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Cook, Katherine M., May 8, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Exner, M.J., June 12, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Jolloway, J.W., Jr., June 12, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., June 14, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Schucker, L.R., June 26, 1924 (Box 3)
  - McMullen, E.W., June 28, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., July 2, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Benson, W.W., July 17, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Burdette, H.S., July 17, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., July 17, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., July 17, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Boykin, James C., Aug. 6, 1922 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Sept. 10, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Nolan, William T., Oct. 2, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Nov. 1, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Nov. 6, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Thomas, D.E., 1924-11-01 (Box 3)
  - Ramsey, E.E., Dec. 29, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Tigert, John J., Dec. 29, 1924 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Jan. 2, 19125 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Jan. 3, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Poundstone, O.C., Jan. 17, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Bethune, Mary McLoud, Jan. 22, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Furgeson, Marion, Feb. 25, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., March 7, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 9, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Papy, Loca E., March 30, 192 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., April 3, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Bigelow,M.A., April 11, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Johnson, Sexton, April 21, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Peebles and Ferguson, Architects, April 23, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., May 6, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Hodge, Maud, May 7, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Kelly, Lessie V., May 14, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Roemer, Joseph, May 15, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Wood,Thomas D., May 15, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., June 5, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Bryan, William Lowe, June 11, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Weary, E.D., June 12, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Roberts, Jack, June 30, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Northrup, W.C., July 2, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Powe and Williamson, July 2, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., July 2, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Zook, George F., July 2, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., July 17, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Aug. 3, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Sept. 2, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Palmore, R.A., Sept. 14, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Palmore, R.A., Sept. 15, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Oct. 3, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Oct. 7, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Bakke, Ella Cyrene, Oct. 22, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Nov. 2, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Reynolds, Nora L., Nov. 23, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Wilbur, G. Elmer, Nov. 23, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Curtis, W.R., Nov. 30, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Nov. 30, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Dec. 2, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Exner, M.J., Dec. 12, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Pleasant, J.L., Dec. 23, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Nash, M.A., Jan. 5, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Broom, J.W., Jan. 8, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Laramy, R.E., Jan. 26, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., Jan. 27, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Feb. 11, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Clark, Harry, Feb. 27, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Feb. 27, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., March 2, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 4, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., March 4, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Bessie A., March 8, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Payne, President, March 8, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Adams, Robert, April 7, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Adams, Robert, April 7, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Kalbach, L.A., April 19, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Laramy, Robert, April 21, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Eicher, Hubert C., May 5, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Young, R.O., July 27, 1926 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, J.F., July 29, 1926 (Box 3)